<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API references on Welcome to Repair App Knowledgebase</title><link>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/</link><description>Recent content in API references on Welcome to Repair App Knowledgebase</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 15:37:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Repairrabbit API?</title><link>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/what-is-repairrabbit-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:41:34 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/what-is-repairrabbit-api/</guid><description>RepairRabbit API will allow you to create a new presentation layer—like an app, a website, or a widget. It can be used to distribute services and information to new audiences. You can easily transfer data to/from different systems and keep it safe. We deliver API for all the RepairRabbit features such as appointments, tickets, inventory, invoice, etc. Thus, you can create a customised solution on top of RepairRabbit API in a secured manner.</description></item><item><title>How to use RepairRabbit API?</title><link>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/how-to-use-repairrabbit-api/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 20:02:37 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/how-to-use-repairrabbit-api/</guid><description>To use RepairRabbit API, you need to whitelist your domains/subdomains (from where you are going to access the RepairRabbit API) with the RepairRabbit.
Whitelisting of the domain is necessary to prevent any unauthorized access to the API. So, Your data can be secured with the RepairRabbit.
The admin of the RepairRabbit can whitelist your domains/subdomains. It can be done from the API Settings of RepairRabbit admin panel.
Click &amp;ldquo;API Settings&amp;rdquo; So, If your application is running at web.</description></item><item><title>What are the core advantages of RepairRabbit API?</title><link>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/what-are-the-core-advantages-of-repairrabbit-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:29:40 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kb.repairrabbit.co/api-references/what-are-the-core-advantages-of-repairrabbit-api/</guid><description>Suppose, you are running a repair business and have a manual process for managing appointments, tickets, stores, inventories, etc. and it becomes messy to manage all those things. At that time RepairRabbit API can help you to build your own customised solution and your own customised UI to serve your needs. If you already have a software solution but are not satisfied with it, we’re here to help. Suppose, you have customers' database saved in another system and you want to move that data to the RepairRabbit application, you can use our API to do it.</description></item></channel></rss>